But in just one day,
it has been pre-ordered a thousand copies in the capital.
How is it?
Miss Zhang's move
is indeed extraordinary.
It will be officially released nationwide tomorrow.
Soon,
you will become the most popular poet.
All this is thanks to Miss Zhang.
But may I ask,
when will I receive my reward?
Don't worry.
It's time to prepare for the poetry club.
If you need,
I'll do my best.
This,
take a few back to Mr. Su.
Thank you for your concern.
My wife doesn't like reading.
And Mr. Su is busy with swordplay all day,
so you should have no time to read.
Take it slow.
Be careful.
Sir,
what are they doing?
You don't know yet?
The bookshop's business
will all be mine from now on.
Fu Xiang,
what underhanded tricks have you used this time?
I earned it fair and square.
Unlike some people,
who uses their husband
to attract clients.
Say that again if you dare!
Oh, oh, oh.
Alright, alright.
How about this?
If the Su's Shop shuts down,
come work for me as a minor official.
I'll give you a job.
Stop!
Jiao!
Miss Zhang,
I wonder if there was anything
I did wrong in our previous cooperation.
Why do you want to replace Su?
Based on your sword-drawing incident,
I can replace you.
I've always been fair in business.
Since you're not convinced,
I'll give you a chance to compete.
Your agencies can compete.
The winner
will get all the business of the Zhang family.
What do you think?
We'll do whatever you say.
I'm afraid she doesn't dare to compete.
I...
We value our promise.
We shouldn't judge the strength of a business
by force.
See?
I told you.
Are you afraid?
Take your time.
You can go back and make a decision.
Let's go.
Bah!
Hurry up.
Miss Zhang,
why do you want to replace Su?
I'm in business,
not running a charity.
I only looked after the Sus
because you were there.
Now that you're leaving,
I'll choose a more suitable one.
I won't leave the Sus.
You're in a different position now.
Some things
are not up to you.
I've decided
to compete with Fu Xiang.
Fine.
They are bullying us.
Listen to the boss.
He said the boss would win.
You can order me
and my men at any time.
Fu bullied your grandma back then.
You can avenge her by beating his grandson.
Beat him.
I'm also a member of our family.
Okay, it's settled.
I disagree.
Come out with me.
Why don't you let me compete?
Don't you think this is unusual?
This is between escorts.
It's not like writing an article.
There's no need for so many twists and turns.
This is a private martial arts contest,
not like the Nebula Conference.
It's inevitable to use real weapons.
It's too dangerous.
It's none of your business.
But it's all because of me.
Cheng Qi,
don't think you can boss around
just because you're the top
and brought business to the agency.
The Zhang family's business is backed by the Grand Preceptor.
It's not as simple as it seems.
You're about to take over.
Don't stir up trouble now, okay?
You just want me to take over so you can leave.
My mother taught me
Never start trouble, never fear it.
If we just let them bully us like this,
the Escort Agency will be more difficult to establish itself.
Even if I'm forced to do this,
I can't avoid it.
You don't need to
worry about this.
Don't beat around the bush.
My Lord,
the form of the competition proposed by Miss Zhang
is that each agency sends a representative.
Either single or double.
The time is set for five days later.
The location is in the east of the city.
The winner
can get all the business of Miss Zhang.
But the loser
can't engage in related business for five years.
The time is three days before my taking over.
It sounds like she has ulterior motives.
How about
let's not compete.
A promise made must be kept.
If you've agreed, you must compete.
Then,
what if I lose?
I'll compete with you.
Bet with my life.
Okay.
It's settled then.
Isn't this a bit hasty?
No.
Fu Xiang thought I would choose a duel.
But Bai
is unpredictable.
How about waiting for Cheng Qi
and asking for his opinion?
That's right, My Lord.
Let's wait for the son-in-law.
Or we can go find him.
You go.
I won't go.
I heard that
the White Wolf Gang has been seen around Yunjing recently.
He hasn't come back yet.
He didn't become a bandit, did he?
But
he doesn't have the conditions
to become a bandit.
I'll go out for a while.
My Lord, My Lord.
My Lord got drunk in Huayue Tower.
Tang Xin can testify to this.
Drink!
Another pot!
Stop talking!
Yicheng.
I'm here.
I feel bad.
Where is
the dashing and unrestrained
Mr. Cheng?
He's gone.
He's disappeared.
Listen to me.
I'm listening.
I'm so wronged.
Cut the crap.
Stop it.
I'm thinking about her,
but she doesn't want me to do it.
Yicheng,
am I wronged?
Don't say that.
The escort agency is her family business,
but it's also mine.
She can care about it,
but I can't, right?
Don't stop me.
Let me finish.
You...
And...
Are you done?
Come on.
Go open the door.
You drank too much.
You deserve to feel sick.
How did I get back?
What's going on with them?
This...
Son-in-law, calm down first.
Calm down, calm down.
My Lady is preparing to fight against Fu Xiang
with Bai Yanli in a double match.
She still decided to compete.
Anyway, she has to compete.
It's all for the escort agency.
No way.
Don't mind him.
Only I can stop it.
Cheng Qi's book of poetry
is truly extraordinary.
I heard it's even sold to Langyue.
The Princess of Langyue likes it very much.
What do you think
when the envoy from Langyue comes,
how about arranging a poetry recitation?
Your Majesty is wise.
In this way,
we can show our literary strength,
and display the imperial power.
Also, we can cater to their interests,
to show our goodwill.
It's a win-win.
Good, good.
By the way,
I'd like to meet this Cheng Qi.
I'll arrange it right away.
May I ask the official reason
for summoning Cheng Qi?
Does the official need a reason
to meet someone?
Cheng Qi has no official position
or academic achievements.
In my humble opinion,
it would be better to wait until
after the meeting
and the rewards.
Your Majesty loves the people like a father.
Mr. Yue is too rigid.
Mr. Yue is thoughtful.
All right.
Later.
Or the censors
will submit memorials again.
Lord Yue is worried that Cheng Qi will be favored.
His enemy will return to the court.
He's just settling personal grudges.
The narrow-minded scholars
are all the same.
Father, about the speech,
prepare well.
You must shine before the royals.
So, Cheng Qi
should stay in the shadows for now.
No matter what,
he must be under my control.
The others
are just walk-on parts.
Yes.
I'll let him stay in the villa
to prepare.
What?
You like him?
Love
is normal,
but you must know your place.
The Zhang family
doesn't need such a son-in-law.
Yes,
I understand.
You may leave now.
Okay.
Good words.
Keep going.
Help yourself.
Okay.
Come on, eat.
Eat some meat.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
I'm preparing for a very important
speech.
You're distracting me.
I didn't say anything.
Anyway, don't show up in front of me.
Gong Xifaca!
Take him away!
Wait...
My lady!
I'm sorry, my lady!
Take these away!
Is she still mad at me?
I know.
But why is she mad?
I wonder too.
Why don't you just tell her
you want to marry her again
and stay in the capital?
Maybe she'll be happy then.
I thought so too.
But now,
I'm not sure if I should mention it.
Why?
She never wanted to marry me.
Yes.
I'm good at writing,
but she doesn't like reading.
I like elegant things,
but she's good at martial arts.
Sounds like a good match.
I think so too.
But
she keeps bringing up our divorce.
Qixi Festival is coming up.
Why don't you just ask her
if she still loves you?
Keep going.
That's all.
My brother said you're in a hurry.
What's up?
Your brother said
he wanted to watch fireworks with me in the room.
Which one looks better,
this one or that one?
Is this the emergency?
Yes.
It's our first Qixi Festival together.
How important is that?
Watching fireworks indoors,
do you really need to think about what to wear?
Do you understand the concept of a special occasion?
This one is for you.
I don't celebrate Qixi Festival.
Then what kind of Qixi gift do you want?
What's wrong with mentioning it?
I really have everything I need.
Then you can try to be in need.
Then...
Roasted chestnuts.
The one we used to go to eat when we were young.
You want to eat roasted chestnuts on Qixi Festival?
The one who sells chestnuts is elusive every day.
Who knows where he'll set up the day after tomorrow?
The day after tomorrow?
It's Qixi Festival.
Right.
Oh, no.
I promised Pax a night tour the day after tomorrow.
It's really bad.
Brother Pax
Long time no see.
We are short of hands recently.
When can you come?
Hello,
I'm here to buy clothes.
You've been doing well recently.
You're familiar with the store anyway. Feel free to look around.
I'll take this one.
This one has been taken by another gentleman.
He's trying it on right now.
I'll look around some more.
Hey, shopkeeper.
I'd like to try on that white one.
Sure.
I'll take
this white one.
No need to try it on.
Just wrap it up.
Choose between the clothes and your life.
In broad daylight,
what can you do to me?
Mr. Cheng.
Mr. Cheng, a cheerful disposition brings wealth.
This gentleman is also an old friend of mine.
It's rare for him to visit.
How about this one
just let him have it?
No way.
I'll buy it no matter how much it costs.
30 taels.
Just do me a favor today.
Let him have it.
Mr. Cheng
Actually, I like Cheng Jiao and her husband.
I have a dress for you.
It's hand embroidered.
Well, shopkeeper
Why don't you give it to me earlier?
I want you to stay in my shop
stay here a little longer.
Come here, my son-in-law.
What's the matter? So mysterious.
My son-in-law,
Tomorrow is the Qixi Festival.
Did you ask My Lady to the lantern show?
I'm just about to tell her about it.
Then hurry up.
I heard that My Lady
will visit the lantern show with Bai tomorrow.
What?
How much money did you owe?
You dare to run up a tab at Huayue Tower.
I really admire your courage.
It's none of your business.
If you pay the bill for me,
I'll buy you a drink.
Otherwise,
go away.
There is a chance to make money.
I don't know if you want it.
What opportunity?
Be my subordinate.
Go away.
Bodyguard Agency.
Didn't you look down on me before?
Besides,
how much money can you give me?
You should know that
if I win this competition,
not to mention Zhang Xi Yun's business,
all the business in the capital
will be mine.
And then?
Then,
I'll give you a part of the business.
Listen carefully, it's for you,
not for Su's Escort Agency.
Is there such a good thing?
Do you want it?
Yes.
Then listen carefully.
What can make Su Yuejiao
leave the Escort Agency
or
never be an escort?
I can.
My Lord.
Where did he go?
Jiaojiao,
this is for you.
No, no, no.
Su Yuejiao,
this is what my mother left me.
No, no, no.
Jiao,
this is for you.
I'll give you mine too.
What am I saying?
Alright, stop eating.
Leave some for me.
Would they really hide the young master here?
Today is the Qixi Festival.
Two men are eating seeds together.
There must be something wrong.
But the three of us
are also looking for him here.
Cheng Yicheng,
why don't you go on a date with your busy lady?
It's such a good day today.
She has to do business.
Come on.
Three, two, one.
Go, go, go.
Aren't we going for a night out?
Or do you want
to just stand here all night?
I have something to tell you.
Then go ahead.
Have you eaten your bowl?
I... I haven't.
No, wait.
Have you eaten your meal?
No, have you eaten dinner?
Didn't you eat together at the Escort Agency?
Excuse me.
Sorry.
My son-in-law,
Bai Yanli is really vicious.
He's just afraid you'll ruin his plans.
I didn't expect the boss to agree to let him come.
What if Mr. Su just wanted to refuse him?
Why are you here?
Didn't you say you were going to sell lanterns?
Making money is indeed important to me,
but now,
you are the most important.
I'm so touched.
I thought
you were used to putting me behind making money.
Come on.
Look at this lamp.
Be good.
Done.
This is
the only thing my mother left me.
For so many years,
I didn't even sell it when I was starving.
Because I want to give it to
the person I like.
Cheng Qi.
What are you doing?
Here's the thing.
I was afraid it would get cold,
so I kept it covered.
Maybe I ran too fast just now,
and this is all that's left.
Try it.
You did all this just to give me this?
Well, I got it.
You can go now.
Wait.
Can't you just stay here?
Why?
I'm your husband.
I should be the one celebrating Qixi with you.
After I take over the position,
you won't be my wife anymore.
I've already married you,
and we've shared a bed.
You'll always be my wife.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Who shared a bed with you?
We did consummate
in Ning'an.
You're a scoundrel!
That doesn't count!
Fine,
I'll talk to my parents,
and we'll get a house.
Then I can marry you
properly.
Why do I have to marry you?
Because I love you.
I know
you have feelings for me.
What...
What do you mean?
At that time,
you came to the Escort Agency
for the Nebula Conference.
That was then.
Now is now.
Anyway,
I'll marry you.
I'm counting on you.
Su Yuejiao,
I'm serious.
The day I met you
was the beginning of all fate.
Your appearance
is the best arrangement of God.
I like you.
Because I like you,
I care about your hobbies.
I worry about where you've been.
Because I like you,
I care about
whether you really want to divorce me.
I don't want to divorce you.
I want to spend the rest of my life with you.
You...
If you ever hurt me...
I wouldn't dare.